Thomas Hart Photographs MS093
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1966 -- 1983; MS093.001; 248 Digital Object(s)
  - The cannon, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04986; Hart, Tom
    Monuments
  - Paige Hall, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04987; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04988; Hart, Tom
  - Goddard Chapel, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04989; Hart, Tom
  - Barnum Hall and Dana Laboratory, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04990; Hart, Tom
  - Packard Hall, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04991; Hart, Tom
  - Ballou Hall, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04992; Hart, Tom
  - Goddard Chapel, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04993; Hart, Tom
  - Wessell Library, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04994; Hart, Tom
  - Stairs leading to Richardson House, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04995; Hart, Tom
    Stairs
  - Cohen Arts Center, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04996; Hart, Tom
  - Arlene Peietkewicz, J1974, homecoming, 1972; MS093.001.DO.04997; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Peietkewicz, Arlene
  - Crowd at homecoming game, 1976; MS093.001.DO.04998; Hart, Tom
    Crowds; People; Events
  - Fraternity cannon, homecoming, 1976; MS093.001.DO.04999; Hart, Tom
    Monuments; People
  - View of football field, homecoming, 1976; MS093.001.DO.05000; Hart, Tom
    Football; Events; People
  - View of football field, homecoming, 1976; MS093.001.DO.05001; Hart, Tom
  - Oscar Porter, A1969, homecoming, 1976; MS093.001.DO.05002; Hart, Tom
    People; Events; Porter, Oscar
  - Hillside House parade float, homecoming, 1976; MS093.001.DO.05003; Hart, Tom
    Events; People; Parade floats
  - George Ross and Bob Methellis, homecoming, 1976; MS093.001.DO.05004; Hart, Tom
    People; Events; Ross, George; Methellis, Robert
  - Steve Costa, E1968, left, Frank Tomaszewki, A1968, and Joe Pedulla, E1969, homecoming, 1976; MS093.001.DO.05005; Hart, Tom
    People; Events; Costa, Steven; Tomaszewki, Frank; Pedulla, Joseph
  - Russell Collins, E1974, with other Tufts students, Hillside House lawn, homecoming, 1976; MS093.001.DO.05006; Hart, Tom
    People; Events; Collins, Russell
  - Richard Squillicioti and Peter Viris, homecoming, 1976; MS093.001.DO.05007; Hart, Tom
    People; Events; Squillicioti, Richard
  - Hillside House kitchen, Bob Lee, right, homecoming, 1976; MS093.001.DO.05008; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Events; Lee, Robert
  - David Gold, A1969, and Oscar Porter, A1969, 1976; MS093.001.DO.05009; Hart, Tom
    People; Gold, David; Porter, Oscar
  - Gordon Dobey, David Gold, Oscar Porter, and Peter Wadler pushing a car that was stuck in snow on College Ave, illuminated by headlights, 1976; MS093.001.DO.05010; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Dobey, Gordon; Gold, David; Porter, Oscar; Wadler, Peter
  - Hillside House football team in red shirts, 1967; MS093.001.DO.05011; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House marches to chariot race on Professors Row, 1967; MS093.001.DO.05012; Hart, Tom
    People; Events
  - Hillside House sedan chair, Jay Hochberg, Don Trites, and Wayne Prescott, 1967; MS093.001.DO.05014; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Marches; Hochberg, Jay; Trites, Don; Prescott, Wayne
  - Hillside House on march, 1967; MS093.001.DO.05015; Hart, Tom
    People; Marches
  - John Marrs and Gerry Sullivan (back facing camera), 1967; MS093.001.DO.05016; Hart, Tom
    People; Events; Marrs, John; Sullivan, Gerry
  - Tufts students, winter carnival, 1967; MS093.001.DO.05017; Hart, Tom
    Students; People; Events
  - Winter carnival, looking down Professors Row, 1967; MS093.001.DO.05018; Hart, Tom
  - Jay Hochberg inside cart, in winter carnival race, 1967; MS093.001.DO.05019; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Races; Hochberg, Jay